# **Ankit Rane**

anks.rane@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/ankit-rane

**©** +91 8082466900

## **Summary**

Experienced UI developer having hands-on experience in designing, implementing and developing quality designs & architecture. Wanted to work on challenging task which provides and opportunity to enhance my skills and knowledge, this could provide me an insight into new aspects.

## **Professional Experience**

## Here Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Airoli, Mumbai

**Spatial Data Specialist** 

June 2019 - Present

- Responsible for analysing and editing Geo-Spatial Data points in Highly Automated Driving (HAD) project
- Creating and maintaining an internal team performance dashboard
- Working with agile methodologies practices including Agile, Scrum using tools such as JIRA and Confluence
- Maintained high discipline and norm adherence, coordinated with superiors of Quality teams, and provided innovative suggestions to improve operational functioning of the internal team
- Part of DEO Developer Community from January 2021
- Created highly responsive user interfaces ensuring best experience on various screen sizes
- Maintained Validations using Java based Code

### Techflux (a Division of Renam Technologies pvt. ltd.)

Vashi, Mumbai

**Software Developer** 

January 2018 - July 2018

- Webapp Development on "Bubble.is" Platform. Customizing those using Web Technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Converted designs & wireframes to high quality UI code
- Planning and Conceptualizing product

### **Abhay Tech Solutions LLP**

**Internship Trainee (Technical Writer)** 

Marol, Mumbai July 2017 – September 2017

• Designed UML Structure for Existing and Future Project

## **Education**

•	Mumbai University	2014 - 2017
	Computer Engineering	5.88 CGPI
•	Shreeram Polytechnic, Airoli	2010 – 2014
•	•	62.26%
	Computer Technology	02.20%
•	S.V. Joshi High School, Dombivli	2001 – 2010
	S. S. C.	77.09%

# **Technical Skills**

Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, SQL

• Technologies: HTML, CSS, Git

## **Projects**

#### **URL Shortener**

- Webapp for Converting Long URL to Short URL
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL

### XML to JSON Parser

- Convert XML file to Formatted JSON File
- <u>Technologies</u>: Java

#### **Business Website**

- Standard Landing Page for Small Logistics Business as a Part of Small Assignment
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

#### **User Profile**

- Standard Landing page about myself to showcase about my Skillset. (Last Updated 2020)
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Reference Link: https://github.com/anksrane/project.git

## **Interest**

• Cricket

Movies

Photo Editing